The sentence is strike now and press the bell.
Hello, hello friends, welcome to the
stock rate YouTube channel. Friends, today we are going to talk about
ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company. There
may be a rise in the stock tomorrow. Also tell us the reason for the rise. Guys,
such numbers in research from the bigg boss side
and there are buyers of Indian stocks. So, those who are waiting for the
general insurance
business of waiting will not completely buy it. So,
due to this, sir, there may be a rise in the stock tomorrow.
So today we will discuss its fundamentals
and
we will also talk about whether you should invest in it or not.
Please watch the video till the end. If you are on the channel for the
first time, then subscribe. If you
want to know about any other company, then
please like the channel and comment. If you
look at the last one month, there is a decline of only 0.1
percent in 6 months. There is
no decline at all even in 6 months. We used to look at it in 0.1 and 1 year.
In one year, there is still a plus of so much and
even after this, there is a plus of 7 percent. If we look at the 5 year
mark, although it is not fit,
but in 2017  It was listed and
by 2030 it doubled the money in 3 years, you
can see that when it was listed,
its price was above 106, in
2017, you had made an investment in WhatsApp Dixit at the price of ₹14100
and
after that, there was a fall in the entire market in February and March,
so if we
look at it, the money had almost doubled
but due to the fall, the head is down again, so we
will talk to Chunnu about it, now let's see, there is a long list of people
buying Bhartiya, the general insurance business of non-life insurance, the people
buying Bhartiya, and after this, the one who will become the third
largest player, such a number, will
become the third largest company in the market in
general insurance, if
I can see the return papers of the company, then there was
no return in the last one month
and look at the three months, there was 365 and a half, after that,
14% in one year and 4% in two years,
digital should be visible here, the listing of 3 years ago is
not here, the
quality of education  You
can see the nuts of 2019-2020 that in 22-24 June 2019,
I still made a big operating
profit of 10 crores, 519,832 operating
profit of last 9 crores and there has been a rise of 9828 percent
and the profit margin is first and
25-50 percent operating profit
margin is lying here, the
selected person will see that the
soil of going to Lombard General Insurance is with 1%
promoters and the promoter is
ICICI Bank Limited, the second
largest bank in the world and
what kind of bank of yours is the most
call giving share in the whole world, after that
give it inside mutual fund at 10:30 and Africa is
favorite 6 to 7 26 percent, so
how much does the public have, only 67 percent, this 8 percent
public has holding here
that the governments have bought 1440, now take it out, the
market remained at 805,
but still there is
less fall in insurance companies because the insurance sector has
come to lose  There are a lot of
features in the market right now, you can see
58,707 crores and pistol squats from company stores, out of
which seven or eight
percent are available in this market, very
few shares are available in the market, so tomorrow it will rise further and go higher,
then you can be impressed,
if you have this Pearson in Holi, then you are a
footpath businessman, however,
from other companies like igseller app and SBI Life, if you
look at the high and date, then 450 crores till Z, which is
not a big deal for you, so much time, if you
see the performance of the fraud company, then you can see, you have to
search here, which is doing 22 percent in the last 15 years, 30 percent
in three years, 25
percent increase in
profit, but you can see 20 percent
and 17 percent return on
equity and retired captain, although I had seen
return on equity, it was 20 percent, 21 percent
and 20% and retirement actress in 1 year,
then 350  Percent or
you can think of a lot, episode
368, you can see in 3 years, eight percent increase
and in 5 years, 27 percent increase in turn-on
capital employed, there will hardly be anyone in the market
who can compete with him and the
fundamentals are very strong
and if you want to know about any other video or want to
know about any other topic then please comment below the channel, if you
like the video then like it, for the
first time on this channel, you must have subscribed.